Artur Kulik

Birthday: 08/03/1985 (35 y.o.)

Tel: +38050-690-70-90

E-mail: arthur.kulik@gmail.com

Skype: <u>arthur_kulik</u> Site: <u>mycmdline.com</u>

Lviv, Ukraine



Summary

The main specialization is Python with about 4 years of experience. Some DevOps related experience - less than 1 year. Networking related experience - 5+ years. Total experience in IT - 13 years. Key technologies: Core Python, Linux/Unix, Networking, Code Quality, Python project infrastructure. Earned two certificates Python3.4 and IBM DataScience.

Technical skills

- Programming languages: Python, Shell, HTML, CSS
- Platforms: Mac OS X, Linux
- Automation tools: Selenium WebDriver (Python)
- CI/CD: Jenkins
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Issue Tracking: Jira
- Web Frameworks: Django, Sanic
- Networking: TCP/IP, Routing, Switching, Sockets
- Data Science
- CVS: Git

Experience

12/2019 - Present, Python Developer (Grid Dynamics)

Development, Support, Bug Fixing of Rule-Based System and ETL/ELT workflows.

Technologies:

- Data Science
- Amazon AWS Cloud
- Snowflake
- Airflow

02/2019 – 12/2019, Python Developer (Softserve)

Development, support, and bug fixing of microservices (REST APIs) for a pharmaceutical domain. Those microservices designed to be a part of an app for managing rebates and fees for pharmaceutical manufacturers. Worked a lot to improve the code quality of the existing code. I also started initiatives for the Python Community, like weekly tech talks.

Responsibilities:

- Troubleshooting/Bug fixing
- Estimating features and change requests.
- Developing functionality: from specifications review and coding to unit testing and deployment
- Performing code reviews
- Participating in backlog refinement, planning, and demos
- Participating in solution architecture design and implementation

Technologies:

Asyncio, Sanic, Static Code Analysis, Integration Tests, Flake8, PySpark.

05/2017 – 02/2019, Python Developer (Datamart)

Development, bug fixing of existing code. Implementation and support of functional tests. Healthcare domain.

Responsibilities:

- Troubleshooting/Bug fixing.
- Estimating features and change requests.
- Developing functionality: from specifications review and coding to unit testing and deployment.
- Performing code reviews

Technologies:

Django, Pytest, Flake8, Selenium, Docker.

01/2016 - 05/2017, Python/PHP Developer / SEO / SMM (Own startup)

Founded a small startup. Involved in every process related to delivering commercial websites.

Development of the desktop application for content writers.

Development software for deploying static web sites.

Automation of various SEO/SMM tasks by using Python.

Different management activities.

Responsibilities (tech only):

Web sites development (Woocommerce)

- Desktop app development (Python/QT)
- Automation by using Python
- Development of scrapers and parsers for SEO/SMM

Technologies:

Core Python, QT, Selenium, Requests, BeautifulSoup, PHP, Wordpress, Woocommerce.

06/2015 - 12/2015, Devops (Sharpminds)

Supporting, Deploying, and Troubleshooting of web sites.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain web servers (Apache, Nginx).
- Maintain DB servers (MySQL, PostgreSQL).
- Update server software.
- Deploy web sites.

Technologies:

Apache, Nginx, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

10/2014 – 06/2015, Python Developer / DevOps (Freelance)

Freelance on Upwork.

Developing REST API (Flask)

Developing scrapers and parsers.

DevOps tasks.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain web servers (Apache, Nginx).
- Maintain DB servers (MySQL, PostgreSQL).
- Maintain cloud infrastructure (AWS)
- Update server software.
- Deploy web sites.
- Develop scripts, tools, scrapers, parsers in Python.

Technologies:

Core Python, Requests, BeautifulSoup, Flask.

03/2012 – 10/2014, PHP/Python Developer (T-Expert)

Full-time software engineer for Medical Centre.

Development of Patient Management Software.

Automation by using Python and Bash.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain web servers (Apache, Nginx).
- Maintain DB servers (MySQL, PostgreSQL).
- Update server software.
- Deploy web sites.

Technologies:

PHP, Yii framework, Core Python, Bash.

12/2008 - 03/2012, Lead Network Engineer (Veles)

Maintain network services, servers, and equipment for Internet Service Provider. Design Network Architecture.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain web servers (Apache, Nginx).
- Maintain DB servers (MySQL, PostgreSQL).
- Update server software.
- Deploy web sites.

Technologies:

Linux, Unix, Networking.

12/2007 – 12/2008, System Administrator (Transmost)

Support, Maintain, Set up PCs, and other equipment for the corporate network.

Responsibilities:

- Setup PC and Software for employees.
- Maintain Windows 2003 Servers and corporate services.

Technologies:

Windows Server 2003, Active Directory, LDAP, Microsoft Internet Security and Acceleration Server, CCTV equipment.

10/2006 – 12/2007, Network engineer (Veles)

Build a physical network for internet access for customers.

Responsibilities:

Install and setup network equipment.

Configure network, routing, etc.

Technologies:

Networking, TCP/IP, Network Security, Routing, Switching

Education and Certificates

- 2002 2007, Computer Science, Chernivtsi National University
- 2007 2009, Finance, Chernivtsi Institute Of Trade And Economics
- 2019, Python 3.4 Certificate, Brainbench
- 2020, IBM Data Science Certificate, Coursera

Languages

• English - B1